The hi my name is katy beslado
こんにちは、Katie Besladoと申します。
i'm the director of ibm quantum strategy
IBMクオンタムのストラテジー担当ディレクターです。
and applications research i'm here to dispel
アプリケーション研究も担当しています。今日は
as many cotton computing this
量子コンピューティングに関するよくある誤解を
as possible in sixty seconds.
できるだけ多く、60秒で解消したいと思います。
The one of the beautiful absolute real
量子コンピューターは本物で、実在します。
and we have devices on the ibm cloud now that anyone can access.
IBMクラウド上にデバイスがあり、誰でもアクセスできます。
Yes but only for certain things they're really good at doing
はい、でも特定のことに限ってです。得意なのは
super complicated math like the universe runs on
宇宙の仕組みで使われるような、超複雑な計算です。
but if you want to do spreadsheeters than an email use
ただし、スプレッドシートやメールであれば
your pc.
普通のPCをお使いください。
Yes theoretically but not
理論上はそうですが、
for a while no one makes the computer good enough to do that
しばらく先の話です。それができるほど優れたコンピューターはまだ存在しません。
yet for the foreseeable future were on track
当面の間は、着実に進歩しています。
and when we get there we're gonna change the way we protect
そして、そこに到達したとき、私たちは情報の守り方を
information.
大きく変えることになるでしょう。
The completely false quantum computers
それは完全に間違いです。量子コンピューターは
are fundamentally different
根本的に異なるものであり、
and use the laws of nature to process information
自然の法則を使って情報を処理します。
today's ai run on good old fashioned classical devices
現在のAIは従来のクラシカルなデバイスで動いていますが、
but we do believe they'll partner in the future.
将来は両者が連携すると考えています。
Not true we have a tremendous ego system
そうではありません。私たちには充実したエコシステムがあります。
of start up academia national absent industry partners that
スタートアップ、大学、国立研究所、産業パートナーが
are using our devices every day the.
毎日私たちのデバイスを活用しています。
No corner inspired has been around
いいえ、「量子インスパイアード」は
for a long time and runs on classical devices they
長い歴史があり、クラシカルなデバイスで動くものです。
won't ever deliver on the promise of corner computing
それでは量子コンピューティングの真の可能性は実現できません。
if you wanted you commuting you have to do it with real quantum
本当の量子コンピューティングを求めるなら、本物の量子
computers
コンピューターで行う必要があります。